https://adampuchtawine.com/privacy-policy/%20

Privacy Policy
“At Adam Puchta Winery Privacy Is Paramount!”
Privacy Policy
At Adam Puchta Winery we are professionally committed and morally bound to protecting your privacy and integrity at all costs.  We take all reasonable steps to protect all data and information supplied to us by our customers. We protect our customers’ privacy by using industry accepted security and data transfer methods to protect against the loss, misuse, abuse and alteration of data in our care.
This Privacy Policy is designed to ensure the safety and accuracy of our customers’ and prospects’ informational assets, whether gathered on this site or by our customers. Any information shared with us will never be given or sold to third parties. We understand the value of information security.
Our marketing initiatives bring us into contact with consumers and businesses. Therefore, integrity is absolutely critical to our long-term success. Adam Puchta is a winery that holds privacy and security paramount.
Adam Puchta Winery does collect both voluntary personal information and automated non-personally identifiable data from internet users, visitors and registrants. We use this information qualitatively to improve our visitors and our own efforts and functionality. Visitors who opt-in to receive information from Adam Puchta Winery or our agents, will only receive appropriate and requested communications.
Adam Puchta Winery utilizes the industry’s leading security solutions, policies and procedures to ensure the physical and electronic security of data stored by Adam Puchta Winery. All of our email contacts are part of a CAN Spam compliant permission based marketing solution that, uses and requires permission-based marketing principles of its clients.  Adam Puchta Winery will communicate only to users who affirmatively express a documented interest in receiving e-mails relevant to their interests. Permission must be ongoing, dynamic and revocable. If a recipient chooses to opt-out, Adam Puchta Winery is required to stop sending messages to that recipient.
Adam Puchta Winery utilizes Cookie and ASP technology for the purposes of traffic analysis such as the time/date of the visit, the time/date of last visit, the page(s) viewed, the referrer, transaction information for e-Commerce pages, and other data. Adam Puchta Winery tracks click-thru behavior in the e-mails it sends out. This data is used to update specific user-profile information, ascertain the areas of most interest to opt-in e-mail recipients, and to personalize messages.
Again Adam Puchta Winery does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information whether gathered by Adam Puchta Winery itself or received from its agents. Adam Puchta Winery is a general audience site and is not directed to youth under the age of 21. Adam Puchta Winery E-mail will not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from or about anyone under 21.
Adam Puchta Winery will make the best effort to comply with privacy laws and adhering to the highest industry standards on privacy.
If you have received unwanted or unsolicited e-mail sent via our system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward that e-mail with your comments to info@adampuchtawine.com for review.
If you would like to unsubscribe from ALL Adam Puchta winery E-mail Marketing lists, please unsubscribe by clicking the link in your email communication.
We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time.
This policy was last updated 06-30-2014.
For Adam Puchta Winery:
Grill Your Own Steak Night & Fish Fry and 165th Anniversary Celebration!
This is going to be a special night because not … Continued
Recent Posts
2020 Oktoberfest 1855 Cellar Bistro Menu
October 2, 2020
Grill Your Own Steak Night & Fish Fry and 165th Anniversary Celebration!
September 23, 2020
Adam Puchta Winery
1947 Frene Creek Rd, Hermann, MO 65041(573) 486-5596
Winery Hours
Sunday-Thursday 11 a.m.-4 p.m.
Friday-Saturday 10 a.m.- 6 p.m.
1855 Cellar Bistro Hours
Wednesday-Thursday 11 a.m.-2 p.m.
Friday-Saturday 11 a.m.-6 p.m.
Contact Us for More Information:
